A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, International Division, Education and Public Policy Division, Office Files of Richard Sharpe FA557
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Choronological Correspondence, 1974-1981; I
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Jun 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Jul 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Aug 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Sep 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Oct 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Nov 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Dec 1979 (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Jan 1980 (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Feb 1980 (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Mar 1980 (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Apr 1980 (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, May 1980 (Box 1)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Jun 1980 (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Jul 1980 (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Aug 1980 (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Sep 1980 (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Oct 1980 (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Nov 1980 (Box 2)
  - 1980 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Dec 1980 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Jan 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Feb 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Mar 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Apr 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, May 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Jun 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Jul 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Aug 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Sep 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Oct 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1981 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Nov 1981 (Box 2)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, A-I (Box 2)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, J-P (Box 2)
  - 1977 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Q-Z (Box 2)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, A-L (Box 2)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, M-R (Box 2)
  - 1978 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, S-Z (Box 2)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, A-G (Box 2)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, H-M (Box 2)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, N-P (Box 2)
  - 1979 Chronological Correspondence/Memoranda, Q-Z (Box 2)
- Public Policy and Social Organization Meetings, 1969-1981; II
  - Public Policy and Social Organization Meeting Minutes, Agendas and Materials, 1973-1981; II.1
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 4, 1973 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), Oct 4, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 20, 1973 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), Dec 20, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 10, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), Jan 10, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 31, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), Jan 31, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 21, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), Feb 21, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 21, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), Mar 21, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 18, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), Apr 18, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 15, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials) (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 14, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, reports and related materials), Jun 14, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 19, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jul 19, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of August 22, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Aug 22, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 20, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Sep 20, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 17, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Oct 17, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 14, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Nov 14, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 11, 1974 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Dec 11, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 9, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jan 9, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 6, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Feb 6, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 20, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Feb 20, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 28, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Mar 28, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 1, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 15, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 13, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jun 13, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 23, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jul 23, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 25, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Sep 25, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 30, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Oct 30, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 25, 1975 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Nov 25, 1975 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 8, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jan 8, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 2, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Feb 2, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 4, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Mar 4, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 1, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Apr 1, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 14, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Apr 14, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 18, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 16, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jun 16, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 29, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jul 29, 1976 (Box 3)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 9, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Sep 9, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 12, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Oct 12, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 10, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Nov 10, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 15, 1976 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Dec 15, 1976 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 11, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jan 11, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 17, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Feb 17, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 31, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Mar 31, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 28, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Apr 28, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 21, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jun 21, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 28, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jul 28, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 19, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Sep 19, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 18, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Oct 18, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 17, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Nov 17, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 15, 1977 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials, incl. David Heaps' report "An Inquiry on the "Values" Project"), Dec 15, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 19, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jan 19, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 16, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Feb 16, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 16, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Mar 16, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 20, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Apr 20, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 18, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 15, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jun 15, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 27, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jul 27, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 14, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Sep 14, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 12, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Oct 12, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 16, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Nov 16, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 13, 1978 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Dec 13, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 24, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jan 24, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 21, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Feb 21, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 27, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Mar 27, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 18, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Apr 18, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 15, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 19, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jun 19, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 24, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jul 24, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 18, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Sep 18, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 16, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Oct 16, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 20, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Nov 20, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 18, 1979 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Dec 18, 1979 (Box 5)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 15, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jan 15, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 19, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Feb 19, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 18, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Mar 18, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 15, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Apr 15, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 20, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 17, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jun 17, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of August 19, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Aug 19, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 17, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Sep 17, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 21, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (1 of 2), Oct 21, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of October 21, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (2 of 2), Oct 21, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of November 19, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Nov 19, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of December 16, 1980 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Dec 16, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of January 20, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jan 20, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of February 17, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Feb 17, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of March 17, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Mar 17, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of April 22, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Apr 22, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of May 19, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials) (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of June 16, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jun 16, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of July 21, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Jul 21, 1981 (Box 6)
    - Agenda and Minutes of September 15, 1981 Meeting (incl.grant proposals, public policy reports and related materials), Sep 15, 1981 (Box 6)
    - PPSO -- Annual Report Notes/Memoranda and Budget Paper for March Board of Trustees Meeting (incl. Henry Ford II resignation letter), 1977 (Box 6)
    - "Report of PPSO Task Force on the Military and Society" by Enid C.B. Schoettle, May 23, 1980 (Box 6)
    - Women's Program Group -- Summary of Meeting (May 30, 1980) with Section on Education and Public Policy, Jun 1980 (Box 6)
  - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Proposals and Recommendations, 1969-1981; II.2
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations, 1969-1973 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations, 1980 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 7)
    - Public Policy and Social Organization Grant Recommendations (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 7)
    - Grants Re: Public Policy Programs at American Universities (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 7)
    - Grants Re: Public Policy Programs at American Universities (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 7)
- Future Program Planning Project, 1975-1976; III
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (1 of 5), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (2 of 5), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (3 of 5), 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (4 of 5), 1975 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File I (Pre-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (5 of 5), 1975 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File II (Post-Mt. Kisco Meeting), 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File II (Post-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (2 of 4), 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File II (Post-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (3 of 4), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- General File II (Post-Mt. Kisco Meeting) (4 of 4), 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- June-July Meetings (Mt. Kisco) -- Summaries, Speeches, etc. (1 of 2), Jun-Jul 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- June-July Meetings (Mt. Kisco) -- Summaries, Speeches, etc. (2 of 2), Jun-Jul 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Key Documents (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Key Documents (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Documents Given to Trustees at June/July Meetings, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Memoranda Re: Foundation Priority Areas, Preparation of FPPP Discussion Papers, etc., 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Board of Trustees -- Outsiders Names Re: Paper Writing, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- Master List, [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Schultz, Theodore -- "The Hungry, Crowded, Competitive World", Feb 26, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Islam, Nurul - "Hungry, Crowded and Competitive World", [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Legesse, Asmarom -- "Hunger and Population", [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Geertz, Clifford and Albert Hirschman -- Conversation Transcript, Jan 27, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- The International Food Policy Research Institute -- Food Policy Paper Summary, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Background -- Oscar Harkavy, Dec 10, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 1. Hungry, Crowded World -- Staff Commentary, [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Silvert, Kalman H. -- "Democratic Non- and Anti-Democrats", 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Kothari, Rajni -- "Democratic Polity and its Future", Feb 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Calabresi, Guido -- "Democracy and the Allocating State", [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Shils, Edward -- "Our Society As It Is", [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Reid, Inez Smith -- "Democratic Polity and How It Works, With Special Reference to the United States", [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Shklar, Judith N. -- "Democratic Customs", [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Whitehead, Ralph Jr. -- "Notes on a Durable Present", Mar 1976 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Background Paper -- Kelly, James A. and Kalman H. Silvert, Dec 15, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 2. Democratic Policy -- Staff Commentary, [1976] (Box 8)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Cardoso, Fernando Henrique -- "Values, Society, and Culture", [1976] (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Tracy, David -- "Values, Society and Culture", Feb 28, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Miller, William Lee -- "The Improvement of the System Within the System", [1976] (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Nozick, Robert -- "Values and Culture", [1976] (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- "Hamilton, Charles V. -- "On Values, Society, and Culture", Mar 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 3. Values, Society -- Background -- Sutton, Francis X., Dec 17, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 4. Knowledge -- Roche, Marcel -- "The Generation of Knowledge and its Spread to Change Society", [1976] (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 4. Knowledge -- Ben-David, Joseph -- "The General and Spread of Knoweldge and its Application to Change in Society", [1976] (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 4. Knowledge -- Kaplan, Martin -- "The Generation and Spread of Knowledge and its Application to Change in Society - For What?", Feb 17, 1976 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 4. Knowledge -- Background -- de Janosi, P.E. and F.C. Ward, Dec 10, 1975 (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 5. Economic Growth -- Haq, Mahbub ul -- "Economic Growth and the Distribution of Economic Opportunity and Benefits Among Men and Nations", [1976] (Box 9)
  - Future Program Planning Project -- Discussion Papers -- 5. Economic Growth -- Johnson, Harry G. -- "Economic Growth and the Distribution of Economic Opportunities and Benefits Among Men and Nations: An Unenthusiastic Contribution Towards Predicting the Intellectual Stock Market", [1976] (Box 9)